本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
翻譯:op
混沌競技場的進展總體來說非常成功
Chaos arena's performance has been a great success
尤其是Asagi和Sakula那場姐妹群奸的場景最受歡迎
Especially the gangbang of Asagi and Sakura
校對:宮雪 園
現場觀眾都沸騰了. 那么我接下來有什么計劃呢？
The audience seem to be having a riotSo we proceed with the plan
壓制:雪夜
Oboro你覺得那個叫做Asagi的女忍者美麗么？
Oboro . Do you think that taimanin called asagi is beautiful?
Black大人
SIR BLACK?
如果她現在就被你這么給弄死了 那不是很可惜了么？
was to die like this now?
我想讓Asagi加入我們的陣營
I want to ask asagi to join our camp.
您這是什么意思？
What do you mean?
我絕對不會同意
I can't accept this
oboro你是一個非常優秀的干部.但是要想留在組織里光想著復仇可是不行的
Oboro, you are a very good subordinate.
But it’s not enough to keep it here for revenge.
這種事情......
That thing.....
Asagi那種女人可能隨時會背叛組織
Asagi could betray us anytime.
以魔鬼的身體活下去.
As a loyalty oath for the devil to survive
你還記得你當初說過的話么？
Do you still remember those words?
Oboro奉獻靈魂給我 我就讓你用惡魔的身體來復活
Oboro dedicated my body to me. I will raise you up.
不要在這樣對待我了.我可是一直對組織忠心耿耿的
Don't do this to me! I have been nothing but loyal to this company.
求求您了
please
Oboro 現在Asagi就是你的同伴了
Oboro .........is now, Asagi is your partner.
black大人！
Sir Black!
你就不怕以后遭到報應么？
Are you not afraid of being punished in the future?
還記得我們已經經常玩的游戲么？
Remember the games we used to do?
當然記得.我只是覺得你你們這種丑八怪性交很惡心.
That's it. I just think you are too ugly.
Oboro這是你答應的的承諾.用來換取以惡魔形態活下去的資格
Oboro, this is your promise to resurrect in exchange for the devil's body.
現在你就是我們的性奴隸了 這個淫紋送給你留念
As a sex slave  need a kinky tattoo of your own
reference
聽說什么？關于Oboro？
Heard what? about Oboro?
今天的標志性商品已經上架了.而且第一天免費
Enn Today's signature goods.Oboro is on the shelves.And free
我聽說了.感謝她來這里 讓這里變得不冷清
I heard of it, thanks to she became lonesome here
真是可憐 連oboro這種地位的人也有今天
Really pitiful... Oboro’s identity is also...
男人都是無腦的. 在被Oboro統治期間一定都積累的許多怨氣
The man really has no brains
and may be retributed after bullying Oboro.
真的么？說實話我還是挺高興的,我討厭Oboro
Really? I feel very happy. Because... I hate Oboro.
因為她統治之下Yomihara變成現在這個模樣
Because her rule Yomihara became like this
哦 看起來 表現已經開始了
The show started
滾開！！我說了 給老子滾開！！！
Go away! I said go away!
你們敢違背我的命令！？你們不怕我報復么？
Don't you know who I am? How dare you disobey me!
你還以為自己是誰呢？你現在只是一個地下世界的性奴而已
Who do you think you are? You are now just a sexual slave in the underground world.
滾 給我滾開
Go away! I said go away!
這個臭婊子總是利用高級惡魔的力量欺負我們
This bitch. Use the power of the superior devil to bully us every day.
這個女人是這里腐敗的根源.是魔物與人類的罪人
This woman is the root of corruption.
It is the sinner of humans and demons.
混蛋們.我是Oboro 我是這個大陸的統治者
Asshole!!!I am Oboro! I rule this land!
婊子給老子閉嘴！嘗嘗這個
bitch shut up take this!
我不會就這樣放棄的.我不會讓你們輕易得逞的.
I will never give in. You won't get away with this!
我受不鳥了
太多了.放我走.
too much let me go
快停下來
Make it stop!
我快受不了了
I can only take so much...ahhnn...
好卑鄙 快停止 停下來
Despicable! Qucik! Stop...stop...stop
好深 塞得滿滿的里面 屄里面和屁眼都被塞的滿滿的
S-so deep...it's filling every bit of my pussy and asshole
我的屁眼被弄的好難受
It's in my ass now too...It feels so...uncomfortable
誰！誰竟敢向我丟雞蛋？！
What!? You dare throw eggs at me??
每年的稅收越來越多.都他媽的因為你
Every year to pay taxes so much！！！Just because of you！！！
你們都會遭報應
Against me, you will all perish!!
你他媽的以為你現在是誰？來過來殺死我啊 臭婊子！
Who do you think you are?Come over and kill me.bitch！
你會后悔的！我會讓你付出代價的
You will regret this. I will make you all pay!!
看你現在那個操行.變成性奴隸還叫囂.死去吧！
Look at your own ！Become a slave！die！！
發出像母豬一樣的慘叫聲.看她高潮了
Squeaked like a pig！！！Her orgasm！
露出了你的真面目
Exposed the true colors
沒想到這么快我們的oboro大人就被干成了這副模樣
I didn't expect this soon, our Oboro sama became this look.